https://cmasolutions.com/privacy-policy/

MenuHomeAboutWho Is CMA?LeadershipNewsCMA CaresCareersCOVID-19 Resources CloseSolutionsStrategyBrandingDigital MarketingWeb and Mobile App DevelopmentSocial MediaPublic RelationsAdvertisingCollateralAssociation ManagementEvents/ConferencesPublicationsAdvertising Sales CloseResultsBlogLet’s Talk
MenuHomeAboutWho Is CMA?LeadershipNewsCMA CaresCareersCOVID-19 Resources CloseSolutionsStrategyBrandingDigital MarketingWeb and Mobile App DevelopmentSocial MediaPublic RelationsAdvertisingCollateralAssociation ManagementEvents/ConferencesPublicationsAdvertising Sales CloseResultsBlogLet’s Talk
Who we are
Our website address is: https://cmasolutions.com.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
Additional information
How we protect your data
What data breach procedures we have in place
What third parties we receive data from
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
SIGN UP FOR CMA ANNOUNCEMENTS
SUBSCRIBE
“I just wanted to thank you for all your efforts for a great Annual Conference for ESPA.
It was truly one of the best I have attended in terms of content, logistics, networking, local hosting, etc! There were so many top-level speakers that were engaging with timely content.
I thought the leadership track was great and something the organization has needed for a long time.
Thanks for all you do to make ESPA so great!
How many associations can claim that nearly 2/3 of their membership attends the Annual Conference?!?
Great job!”
Julie Pingston, CDME, CMP, CTA Executive Vice President & Chief Operating Officer Greater Lansing Convention & Visitors Bureau
“On behalf of IMARK Group and myself, I’d like to thank each of you for your contributions to IMARK Now magazine. Our magazine speaks volumes about the quality of our organization, our members, and our suppliers. Because this is such an important part of our brand, we set a very high standard of excellence. With your leadership and support, we believe we met that standard. We receive many positive comments on our magazine and that makes us feel great.”
Steve Ruane IMARK Group
“I have never been the Chairperson of such an event before and it was made so much easier with all of the preparation and assistance provided by ICMA [CMA] staff. The recruiting and vetting of speakers, all of the logistics of the venue, the preparation of the “script” were all first rate! All this effort created a dynamic event that I think is just the start of a great new membership opportunity for ICMA. I really enjoyed working with all of you on this! You have built a really great organization and I’m proud to be just a small part of it!”
Dave Tushie ICMA Standards Representative and President of Magellan Consulting
“The outcome was even better than expected. Not only the name, MIDJersey Chamber of Commerce, was WOW, but the roll out was superb. And it continues as we re-named our Award winning Business Magazine, Mercer Business to MIDJersey Business. The response has been wonderful.”
Timothy Losch Past Chairman, Board of Directors, MIDJersey Chamber of Commerce
CMA has consistently provided excellent customer service and has followed up and communicated well at every step of our involvement with them.  Their work has been creative and efficient, and we have used them for multiple projects over the last few years.  I can easily recommend them and we intend to continue to use them ourselves.
Marc Saluk Director, Hunterdon County, Division of Economic Development
I consent to CMA collecting my details through this form.
CAPTCHA
Lets see what we can do for you
First NameEmail
PhoneCompanyResults you’re looking for
I consent to CMA collecting my details through this form.
CAPTCHA
×
